You're as popular as ever, Shido.
There's no need to worry.
I don't intend to stir up
trouble in a place like this.
Why should we believe you?
Because if I felt like it
and wanted to resort to violence,
I'd manifest my Angel this very moment.
Taking students hostage
would be as simple as that.
The fact that I haven't done so
is proof I'm not lying.
"February 9th"
You're not here to enjoy
school life, are you?
But believe me, I'd like that.
If so, we'll throw you a welcome party.
After your power is sealed, though.
Sure, that's fine by me.
Eh?
I'm okay with entrusting
my Spirit power to you, however...
There's just one condition.
And that would be...?
Let's talk about it after school.
There're too many people around.
You know why I summoned you:
Zodiac has fallen into Ratatoskr's hands.
Now, Ratatoskr has ten spirits
under its control.
I'm ashamed of myself.
I'm not blaming anybody.
In fact, this situation is everything
I could've hoped for.
Though Sister limits my information,
I can still use Beelzebub to hit
Ratatoskr where it hurts.
It's about time we made it happen:
To use Shido Itsuka as the key
to make the Spirits invert.
Leave it to me.
This time, I'll produce results.
I hope so.
Still, I've prepared
a helper to lend a hand.
Helper?
You mean, a Wizard?
Let me introduce you Nibeelcole,
the daughters of my Demon King!
Start the operation at once.
I expect Shido Itsuka's head
by the end of the day.
Well, I'll get going.
Are you sure, Shido?
Wouldn't it be safer if we came?
Tohka's right. It's dangerous.
If you plan to face a Spirit who's cloaked
in shadow, you need us!
Agreement. We'll come along.
Thanks, but I'll be fine.
It's true that Kurumi is dangerous,
but she won't go back on her word.
Besides, if I can't even talk
to Kurumi one-on-one,
I've got little to no hope of ever
sealing her Spirit power.
All right, Kurumi. I came as promised.
Greetings, Shido.
--Don't push!
--Won't Shido see us?
This morning, I noticed something:
You've changed a bit, Shido.
Eh?
You look like you've matured.
Though, I suppose it's expected
with all the carnage you've lived through.
D-Don't make fun.
Anyway, what's this condition of yours
for sealing your Spirit power?
Okay, okay. I'll tell you.
I...
Are you ready?
Of course. Good to go.
I'm impressed you stopped my attack!
That's Ellen for you!
Mana! Why are you here?!
What is this? Was our plan leaked?!
My, what a scary face!
Keep scowling like that
and you'll get wrinkles!
Artemisia, let's regroup!
Artemisia?
I don't know how you did it,
but well done.
You managed to thwart our plan.
Yeah. It's annoying, actually.
Oh?
So, what now? Looks like
you missed your big chance.
For real? Our turn already?
Whatever, as long as it helps Father.
So, you want us to kill her?
Nibeelcole, it's all you.
Yeah, yeah.
--See you later!
--Bye bye!
Not so fast!
--My, my!
Nightmare!
Eww, what's that?
They all have the same face! Creepy!
Like we're one to talk!
I can help if you're struggling, Mana.
I hate seeing the weak get picked on.
Watch your mouth! I'll lop it off
along with your head!
My, my! Should you really be
acting tough right now?
After I'm done killing you, you're next!
Shido...? Shido?
Are you all right, Shido?
S-Sorry. I spaced out there.
Now then, allow me to explain.
My goal is the same as it was before:
You have Spirit power
contained within your body...
...and I wish to devour it.
After all, there are ten Spirits worth
of power stored inside you.
In other words,
you want to kill me, right?
Your goal is to seal my Spirit power,
is it not?
Yeah, but that's not all.
I want you to atone for all
you've done and live a happy live.
That's my-- That's our ultimate goal.
You're too kind, Shido.
But, that's a problem. It's impossible
for our desires to intersect.
Say, Shido...
Rather than both our dreams
staying incomplete,
isn't it better if one of them came true?
That is, even if one of us
loses everything for it.
Don't be afraid.
I don't intend to steal
your Spirit power by force.
I'm willing to do things your way.
Huh?
How about whoever makes the other
fall for them is our winner?
Eh?
If I fall in love with you,
I'll willingly give up my Spirit power.
However...
...if I make you fall in love
with me first, I win.
Then, I get to devour you.
You really think I'm gonna admit
I'm in love knowing I'll die?
I wonder.
I'm confident I can make you say it,
even at the cost of your life.
Are you not confident you can make me
head over heels for you?
All right. You're on.
I'll make you choose me
over everything else.
That's the Shido I know.
Now then, shall we begin our date?
Who said you got to decide?!
If you lose, you die!
Sorry... But I wasn't able
to reach Fraxinus.
I mean, I know you had no choice but to
accept her challenge in that situation.
But knowing it and accepting it
are two different things!
Stupid Big Brother!
You never think of yourself!
Good grief.
Now you have a go.
Letting comms go out at a time
like that means I failed to support you.
If you say so. You sure about this?
Yeah. Do it.
Take this!
You like that?!
And that!
I'll let you off with that.
N-No fair, Shido!
--Shido! We're coming in!
--Sorry we're late!
Addition. We had to change.
About the strategy meeting...
Holy smokes!
Um, uh... This is...
Shido! He...! He...!
There, there. It's okay, Kotori.
Shido! What did you do?!
Dear me! Did we interrupt something?
Hold up! It's not like that!
Doubt. It's not like what?
Are you okay, Kotori?
Aww! Kotori had all the fun!
So, you like little sisters?
I'm glad I prepared
these adoption forms, Big Bro.
This is getting out of hand.
Now that it's calmed down, let's move on.
Shido and Kurumi will be competing
to make the other fall for them.
Though she's after Shido's Spirit power,
she may still appear before you guys.
Be on your guard.
R-Right.
Okay. I won't take a step outside.
You don't have to go that far.
Hmm. It's puzzling.
What is this Kurumi after
by stealing his Spirit power?
She's not after power itself, is she?
Uh, well...
I think I have a good idea
about what Kurumin's goal is.
Eh?
I wasn't trying to hide it, but...
Actually, Kurumin has
come to my place before.
She wanted me to
look things up with Raziel:
About the Spirit of Origin
and how to beat it.
The Spirit of Origin...
Yeah. The Spirit that first
appeared 30 years ago.
She wanted to know where and when
it showed up, and about its power.
In order to kill it.
Kill?
So, her asking about
the exact time and place...
Is to make the Spirit that appeared
30 years ago never happen.
When I got help from Kurumi Tokisaki
in the other world, she said as much.
I see. Kurumi can go into the past.
But to do so, she needs
the power inside Shido.
She'll kill the Spirit of Origin
that appeared 30 years ago...
...and erase it from history.
That's Kurumi's goal.
Argh, jeez! Now there're
even more questions.
Kill the Spirit of Origin?
Why would she do that?
It's dangerous to dig deeper
knowing so little.
It's worthwhile trying to connect
the dots, no matter how small.
True.
But the problem is that
Kurumi's shrouded in mystery.
I've got something I wanna say, too.
Mana! What happened to you?!
It's no big deal. Just some scratches.
Didn't I tell you to sit
your butt in a medical pod?
I gave her permission.
She said she had something
important to say.
Yeah. Take a look at this.
Kurumi's clone army?
I think this fight is what caused
the communications disruption.
Anyway, I managed to thwart DEM.
That's what you said in the report.
What I don't get is how you
predicted Ellen would attack.
Well...
Nightmare... Kurumi Tokisaki told me.
She said that Ellen would be launching
an attack on Big Brother.
She told me exactly where and when...
which was yesterday.
So? Why did the lovely Mana
keep this secret from me?
It's just, I figured you wouldn't let me
go if I said anything, you know?
You know me well. You and I
will have a long talk later.
Ugh! Please spare me!
Back to Kurumi.
Yeah. Why did she tell Mana
that Ellen would attack?
For starters, how did she
know it would happen?
Perhaps she just wanted to protect you.
Tokisaki Kurumi is after
your Spirit power.
She wouldn't be pleased
if DEM got you first.
And she has an army of clones
to gather information.
Maybe she found out
about their plans somehow.
Well, that's true...
Something on your mind, Shido?
Uh, well...
It's nothing. Anyway,
let's prepare for tomorrow.
Wha--?!
Good morning, Shido. What a lovely day.
Kurumi?! Why are you here?!
My, my. Is it odd for classmates
to walk to school together?
Come, let's go.
Reine, we've got trouble.
Understood. Kurumi, right?
She's gone on the offensive.
I'll contact Kotori.
Just play along for now.
Oh, yeah! Kurumi, will you come with me?
I wanna show you something.
Oh? I can't wait to see what it is!
Well then, after you!
This is...?
Where all the local cats gather.
I thought you might like it, Kurumi.
I-I don't know why you'd think that.
C'mon. You, too.
W-Well, if you insist...
It's okay. Don't be afraid.
Wh-What's so funny, Shido?!
Sorry. That wasn't supposed to happen.
C'mon, there's lots of other cats.
Try petting one.
No, thanks. It'll just run away again.
It'll go better this time.
Perhaps you're right.
Hmm?
There, there!
You're right! This little kitten likes it!
Meow!
Shall we say round one ended in a tie?
"Episode 09:
'Nightmare's Seduction.'"
Meow...
Valentine's is here!
Excited girls! Panicking boys!
When the world's fate is involved,
excitement and panic is expected!
Next time: "Girl Time."
Watch it or I'll seal you!
"Episode 10: 'Girl Time.'"